[Music]
okay here we are van Davon Huggins and
my boy Mike Taylor my compatriot and um
compart triarchs it's our second
installment of season two of The
critiquers Corner critiquing Kean peel
episodes on for the entire season of KM
Peele think Mike's gonna get a little
bit more involved You're Gonna Hear Mike
speak more to the camera and stuff like
that I mean lots of stuff going on right
Mike episode two man hey y'all had that
one where the two dudes was moving and
he was talking about the dubstep music
and whatnot I like this wait for the
drop I like this wait for the drop I'm
sorry the
drop you know sometimes I would think
like if you want to like keep your
comedy in the same world you know what
I'm talking about same real me keep it
in the same what it real yeah go tell
them I just said it I could barely hear
it so you may as well have said to the
camera anyway right did you barely hear
it or did you not hear it
he said realm he said realm he said go
into another realm the dude started
going into like this weird slow motion
stuff like why is that happening I
should have gone into the Matrix now you
should There He Go you at least gone
into the Matrix Man not my idea though
you all know that was Mike's idea man
yeah Trinity just go straight Trinity on
that and then Mak and then and then
they both should have been like looking
like Trinity and be like cuz then I
would have been like ah these is
in The Matrix cuz like if a person knows
what's going on all of the time then
it's gets boring you know what I mean it
just gets boring you got to stay ahead
of the you got to stay what's that yeah
got to stay ahead of what the a I don't
know man might as well just say it to
the camera CU I can't understand some
I'm what you got to
step I can't hear what you're saying I'm
saying you let me say yep you got to
stay on him
St okay you know we going to move to the
comments Corner trust me there's going
to be some format changes
definitely this season it's going to
happen I what I don't know nothing about
that we talk the gold Sea the gold
Sea that's tight all right these dudes
look like Chris Cross grown up
this can I just say this to you Doug old
C how's this look like Chris Cross
you just saying stupid Chris Cross
ain't got no full
beard I mean Chris Cross Rick Ross maybe
just for that we reading another comment
all right look like Tyler the
Creator with a beard ha what's with all
the impersonations today about looking
like different people I don't what is he
talking about you do look a little bit
like Tyler the Creator though anyway man
that's our episode for this week we
cannot wait for you to come back next
week when the format's going to have
some changes there's and K and Peele
should have a dick in there too oh also
K and Peele y'all should put a dick in
that dubstep
[Music]
scene if you want to see our videos Man
y'all got to click right here seriously
though it's be right there it's going to
be right there it's be right
there